Guide to the Cornell University Campus Planning Office records,1982-2008.
Cornell University Campus Planning Office records, 1982-2008.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University Campus Planning Office records, 1982-2008.
43-2-687
Cornell University.Campus Planning Office.
2.1 cubic feet.
Records and slides.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University campus planning office records including reports, publications, and other papers relating to planning at Cornell, campus development guidelines, campus landscape design notebooks, a strategic framework for campus precinct development, and other subjects; and slides of campus buildings, includes Cornell University: Campus Landscape Planning and Design, ca. 1980.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Cornell University campus planning office records including reports, publications, and other papers relating to planning at Cornell, campus development guidelines, campus landscape design notebooks, a strategic framework for campus precinct development, and other subjects; and slides of campus buildings, includes Cornell University: Campus Landscape Planning and Design, ca. 1980.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Cornell University--Buildings.; Cornell University--Planning.; Universities and colleges--Planning.
Form and Genre Terms:
Slides (photographs).
INFORMATION FOR USERS
See also Committee on Campus Planning records, #11-4-1694.
See also Plans of Proposed Cornell University Buildings, #43-2-41.
See also Dept. of Building and Grounds records, #43-2-1021.
Access Restrictions:
Building plans are restricted to permission of the office of Planning Design and Construction.
CONTAINER LIST
- Cornell University Campus Plan - Volume I, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Draft Generic Environmental Impact Statement, 1992-05 (Box 1, Folder 2-4)
- Draft Generic Environmental Impact Statement - Volume I Text, 1993-01 (Box 1, Folder 5-7)
- Draft Generic Environmental Impact Statement - Additional Appendices and Reference Material, 1993-01 (Box 1, Folder 8-9)
- Draft Generic Environmental Impact Statement - Volume I Text, 1993-09 (Box 1, Folder 10-15)
- Draft Generic Environmental Impact Statement - Appendices, 1993-09 (Box 1, Folder 16-30)
- Draft Generic Environmental Impact Statement - Volume 3, 1993-09 (Box 1, Folder 31-34)
- Draft Generic Environmental Impact Statement Second Draft Completeness Response, 1993-05 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Generic Environmental Impact Statement, 1994-02 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Final Generic Environmental Impact Statement - Draft, 1994-03 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Final Generic Environmental Impact Statement, 1994-04 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Final Generic Environmental Impact Statement - Memos, 1994-05-06 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Campus Landscape Design Notebook, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Special Areas at Cornell, 1991-04 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Special and Natural Areas at Cornell, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Strategic Framework for Campus Precinct Development, 1992-10 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Strategic Framework for Campus Precinct Development - Precincts 1-3, 1992-10 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Strategic Framework for Campus Precinct Development - Precincts 4-12, 1992-10 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Campus Landscape Planning and Design, 1970-1979 (Box 2)
- Campus Development Guidelines, 1985 (Box 2)
- Cornell Master Plan for the Ithaca Campus, 2008 (Box 3)
- Slides by Jon Reis, 1982-1987 (Box 4)
  - Building greenways for Tompkins County: an action plan, 1995-07; Tompkins County Greenway Coalition (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Campus Planning Key Words: Municipal; Transportation; Pedestrian; Bicycle
- East Ithaca circulation study, 1981-05; O'Brien Taube Associates (Box 5, Folder 2)
  Campus Planning Key Words: Municipal; Transportation
- Pine Tree Road relocation a synopsis of planning and design, 1985-03; Fabbroni, Lawrence (Box 5, Folder 3)
- North south connector, 1983; Campus Planning Office (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Ithaca bikeway technical report, 1975; Cornell Graduate Landscape Architecture Program (Box 5, Folder 5)
  Campus Planning Key Words: Municipal; Transportation; Bicycle
- Ithaca Cornell parking study existing parking demand zoning ordinance parking requirements, 1998-02; Travers Associates (Box 5, Folder 6)
  Campus Planning Key Words: Municipal; Transportation; Parking; Zoning
- City of Ithaca Cornell University Collegetown parking and circulation study, 1982-11; Travers Associates (Box 5, Folder 7)
  Campus Planning Key Words: Municipal; Transportation; Parking
- Central receiving for Cornell University, 1981; Cheeks, James McLoyd, Jr (Box 5, Folder 8)
  Campus Planning Key Words: Transportation; Receiving
- Concept study Plant Science Complex, 1991-02; Wasa (Box 5, Folder 9)
  Campus Planning Key Words: Space; Ag Quad
- Preliminary Arts Quadrangle space utilization study, 1989; Dicke, Eric (Box 5, Folder 10)
  Campus Planning Key Words: Space; Arts Quad
- West Campus planning project conceptual design report, 1995-05; Trowbridge and Trowbridge (Box 5, Folder 11)
  Campus Planning Key Words: Space; West Campus
- West Campus planning project, 1995-05; Trowbridge and Trowbridge (Box 5, Folder 12)
- College of Agriculture and Life Sciences_master plan building use and adaptability, 1993-11; Blackett, Anthony (Box 5, Folder 13)
  Campus Planning Key Words: Space; College Plan
- College of Agriculture and Life Sciences_master plan department program development, 1993-11; Blackett, Anthony (Box 5, Folder 14)
- College of Agriculture and Life Sciences_master plan space analysis report, 1996-04; Blackett, Anthony (Box 5, Folder 15)
- College of Agriculture and Life Sciences space study_executive summary, 2003-02; Dober, Lidsky, Craig and Associates (Box 5, Folder 16)
- College of Agriculture and Life Sciences space study_supporting documents, 2003-02; Dober, Lidsky, Craig and Associates (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Historic building survey of the Lower Campus_a proposed district for the National Register of Historic Places, 1970; Donohue, Mary (Box 5, Folder 18)
  Campus Planning Key Words: Historic preservation; Arts Quad
- School of Hotel Administration expansion study, 2007-02; KSs Architects (Box 5, Folder 19)
- College of Engineering master plan techical report, 1986-07; Bohm-NBBJ Dober and Associates (Box 5, Folder 20)
- College of Engineering space study, 2002-11; Dober Lidsky Craig and Associates (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Game Farm Road Complex development study, 2004-11; Urban Strategies Vollmer Associates (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Cornell University master plan 1988, 1988; Sasaki Associates (Box 5, Folder 23)
  Campus Planning Key Words: Master Plan
- College of Engineering facility study, 1982-03; Dober and Associates (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Collegetown parking study City of Ithaca Tompkins County, 2000-07; Greig, Jessica (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Parking feasibility study, 1983-11; Travers Associates (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Plan of proposed Graduate Student Housing, Undated (Map-case Folder)